Lyubomila Petkova

Location: London Telephone: 07706723018 Email: lubomilag1@gmail.com

Professional profile

A highly motivated individual with technical skills gained from a range of work experience placements across multiple disciplines. Passionate about web development and design. Interested in career opportunities across multiple industries within the technology function. Confident in AWS (cloud computing), HTML, HTML5, CSS,CSS3, MySQL and Pyhton. An adaptable, curious and confident individual who is always keen to learn more!

Career summary

October 2017 - November 2017

Amazon Web Services, London

Work Experience through the re:Start Programme

I was successfully accepted into the AWS re:Start Programme for 2017. This involved 3 weeks of training delivered by QA which covered topics such as cloud computing, agile scrum methodology, Python programming and architecting on AWS.

Following completing the initial training, I was selected by AWS to complete a work experience placement with their UK&I organisation in London.

Whilst at AWS, I had first hand experience of how the commercial team engage with their customers and how the technical team are able to support their customers by providing architectural advice and general AWS experience. I had the chance to attend a number of customer facing events and joined the sales team on customer meetings to increase my knowledge of how technology can enable business of all sizes and all industries.

July 2017 The Bridge At Waterloo, London

Participant in Boot Camp "Digital Futures 2017"

I collaborated in a team, working with physical computing programs like: Crumble, Hummingbird, BBC micro:bit. We digitally enhanced a choreographed performance by using code to create a digital interpretation of the musical composition. This was incorporated by digital interactions within the performance that add to the overall effect for the audience.

As a team leader for a smaller team whilst delivering on our tasks to a larger team increased my leadership/teamwork ability and stakeholder management to ensure all tasks were completed on time and everyone knew what they were responsible for.

January 2017 – June 2017 London Academy of IT, London

Web Designer and Office Admin

Designing demo websites with HTML, CSS and Bootstrap or in WordPress. Teaching one-to-one HTML and CSS for beginners. As an office admin - organizing the environment, making outbound and answering inbound calls, sending emails and printing materials for the office. The work involves using MS Office, Adobe CS and C-panel.

February 2014 – May 2015 Provident Financial, Bulgaria Call Center Loan Officer

Conduct Outbound calls to pre-qualified and retention leads to advise them on Provident specialty products.

Identify goals of In-bound calls, collect information and work with them through the loan process.

Submits completed loan application and supporting documentation to the processing department. Present the advantages and disadvantages of different financial products to determine the best option for each customer's financial situation.

Set proper customer expectations and provide timely status updates to ensure a positive customer experience.

June 2014 – October 2014 CIEE, Maine, USA

Participant in Work And Travel Programme

May 2013 - September 2013 CIEE, Maine, USA

Participant in Work And Travel Programme

Education & qualifications

September 2005 - May 2010

Foreign Language High School "Yordan Radichkov" – Vidin, Bulgaria

References available on request